Willard Mullin Cartoons
Willard Mullin Cartoons
1947-1966
Mullin, Willard, 1902-1978
2.5 linear ft.
American sports cartoonist. Original cartoons, with a few reproductions.
2651144
Biographical History
Willard Harlan Mullin (1902-1978) was an American sports cartoonist and illustrator.
Though born in the mid-west, Willard Mullin spent his formative years in Los Angeles, California, and it was there that he broke into the newspaper business as a staff artist for the Los Angeles Herald in 1923. In 1934, after brief stints with papers in Ft. Worth and San Antonio, Mullin landed with the New York World-Telegram and Sun where he would remain as sports cartoonist for the bulk of his career. Mullin was highly influential and is often cited as a major influence on many of the great sports cartoonists of the following generation, including Karl Hubenthal and Gene Basset. Mullin's career spanned a legendary era in New York sports history, and his images of the great Yankees teams, the Brooklyn Dodgers, the New York Giants and Mets are iconic. Possibly, Mullin's most famous creation was the "Brooklyn Bum," a colorful Dodger fanatic who later followed the franchise west, but he was also noted for his "Mets kid" and "St. Louis Swifty" characters, as well as and his skillful renderings of animals and other team mascots. When the World-Telegram and Sun folded in 1966, Mullin continued doing freelance work, publishing sports illustrations and cartoons in The Sporting News, the Saturday Evening Post and Life, among many others. Willard Mullin received the National Cartoonist Society's prestigious Reuben Award in 1954 and the NCS award for Sports Cartoons eight times (1957-1962, 1964, 1965). In 1971, the NCS named him "Sports Cartoonist of the Century".
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Willard Mullin Cartoons collection contains original and reproduction sports cartoons from the early to mid 1960s. Most of the cartoons deal with New York sports topics including Yankees baseball, Giants and Jets football, the Mets, Madison Square Garden events and horse racing. There are a substantial number of cartoons dealing with boxing, especially the Cassius Clay/Sonny Liston fights of 1964 and 1965. The many New York Yankees cartoons in the collection are particularly representative of the team's 1964 campaign with Yogi Berra as manager, usually noted as the end of the great Yankees dynasty. There are many appearances of the Brooklyn Bum, the Mets kid, the St. Louis Swifty, and many other stock characters and animal mascots.
As the cartoons are not specifically dated, dates listed in inventory are derived from context. Original cartoon: traces of graphite, crayon, zipatone, brush, pen and ink on illustration board, approx. 15 x 22 in.
Arrangement of the Collection
Cartoons are arranged by sport and sorted in alphabetical order by title (or prominent caption, if untitled).
Related Material
has collections of over one hundred cartoonists. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Art -- Cartoonists; Mullin, Willard, 1902-1978.; New York world-telegram and the sun.; American wit and humor, Pictorial.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Cartoonists -- United States.; New York Yankees (Baseball team) -- History -- Pictorial works.; Sports -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Cartoons (humorous images); Cartoonists.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
M12-071 ("...And with three straight Giants losses..."), purchase, 2012.
M13-054 (3 items from 1947, 1 from 1949), acquired 1993, source unknown.
Inventory
*text in brackets taken from prominent caption.
- Baseball cartoons, 86
  - Advice From The Lovelorn, 1961-1966; Mets, Casey Stengel, Mets kid, Mets fans (Box 1)
  - [A.L. Pitching Averages...], 1961-1966; Yankees, Twins (Box 1)
  - All The Answers, 1961-1966; Yankees, George Weiss (Box 1)
  - Allegro, 1961-1966; Mets, Phillies, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Among The Missing, 1966; Yankees, Red Sox, Mickey Mantle (Box 1)
  - Anchors Aweigh, 1965; Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - ...And So To Baltimore, 1966; Dodgers, Orioles, Brooklyn Bum, oriole, 1966 World Series (Box 1)
  - ...And With Three Straight Giants Losses..., Giants, New York, barbershop, Sam Maglie (Box 1)
  - The Antidote?, 1961-1966; Yankees, Athletics, Kansas City, "kissing cousin" (Box 1)
  - Balk!, 1961-1966; Ford Frick, umpires, balk rule, Warren Giles, National League (Box 1)
  - The Best Team I Ever Had, 1965; Yankees, Johnny Keane, Cardinals, St. Louis Swifty, 1965 season (Box 1)
  - Betsy Ross; Circa 1964, Yankees, Yogi Berra, Ralph Hauk, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - Big Boy Now, 1961-1966; Phillies, Bob Carpenter (Box 1)
  - [The Big Hearted N.L. Has A New Plan...], 1961-1966; National League, Warren Giles, labor issues, Mets kid, Colt .45s cowboy, Yankee player (Box 1)
  - Bird Watcher, 1961-1966; Yankees, Orioles, oriole (Box 1)
  - A Bit Warm For A Blanket, 1961-1966; Yankees, White Sox, Red Sox, Orioles, Kansas City Athletics, A.L. 1st division (Box 1)
  - Bombs Away, 1964; Yankees, Yogi Berra, Ralph Hauk, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - [By A Strange Coincidence The Kansas City Athletics...], 1961-1966; Charles O. Finley, Athletics, Kansas City (Box 1)
  - Cinderella...., 1961-1966; Mets, Wes Westrum, Dick Stuart, Marv Throneberry, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - The Compact Job, 1964; Yankees, Yogi Berra, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - The Company He Keeps, 1961-1966; Mets, Giants, Dodgers, Brooklyn Bum, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Easter Egg Hunt, 1961-1966; Al Lopez, White Sox, Yankees (Box 1)
  - Enter The Patsy, 1961-1966; Mets, Giants, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Even Split, 1964; Yankees, Cardinals, St. Louis Swifty, 1964 World Series (Box 1)
  - Flagpole?, 1961-1966; Frank Robinson, Orioles (Box 1)
  - Gilled!, 1961-1966; Gil Hodges, Senators, Yankees (Box 1)
  - Goin' My Way?, 1964; Yankees, Mets, Mets kid, spring training (Box 1)
  - Good Enough Ain't Enough, 1961-1966; Mets, Pirates, Don Cardwell, Mets kid, pirate, "5 errors" (Box 1)
  - Hold That Tiger, 1963; Yankees, Tigers, tiger (Box 1)
  - Home Is The Hero, 1964; Yankees, cab ride (Box 1)
  - Home Coming, 1965; Yankees, Johnny Keane, Twins (Box 1)
  - The Homefires, 1961-1966; Mets fans, radio (Box 1)
  - How-Do, Again..., 1965; Dodgers, Twins, Brooklyn Bum, Willard Mullin, 1965 World Series (Box 1)
  - [It Would Be Our Guess That Old Adage...], 1961-1966; American League playoff picture (Box 1)
  - Jingle Bells, 1961-1966; Yankees, Twins, snowball (Box 1)
  - [Joe Dominguez], reproductions, not originals; 2 items (Box 1)
    Gift of Joseph Trzasko, 2015
  - Manna From Heaven, 1961-1966; Fred Reichardt, Angels, Yankees (Box 1)
  - [The Mets Went Into The Pirates' Den...], 1961-1966; Mets, Pirates, Mets kid, pirate (Box 1)
  - [The Mets Will Never Forget Their Finest Hour...], 1961-1966; Billy Williams, Mets, Cubs, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Monkey Business, 1961-1966; Dodgers, Brooklyn Bum, Walter O'Malley, Walt Alston, Buzz Bavasi, Charlie Dressen, Leo Durocher (Box 1)
  - Nail Everything Down!, 1961-1966; Mets, Braves, Native American figure, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - The 'New Breed'?, 1961-1966; Mets, Braves, Native American figure, Mets kid, "Boston-Milwaukee-Atlanta-wither-so-ever Braves" (Box 1)
  - Next Course!, 1966; Mets, Reds, Opening Day 1966 (Box 1)
  - Non-Objective Painting, 1961-1966; Charles O. Finley, Athletics, Kansas City, American League (Box 1)
  - Not His Dish, 1961-1966; Yankees, spring training, Grapefruit League (Box 1)
  - [Now Is The Time For The General Managers...], 1961-1966; N.L. and A.L. presidents (Box 1)
  - Off And Running...But Not Very Fast..., 1966; Mets, Reds, Yankees, Tigers, Mets kid, tiger, Opening Day 1966 (Box 1)
  - Oh, Say Can You See, 1961-1966; Yankees, Mets, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Ole!, 1961-1966; Yankees, White Sox, wild bull (Box 1)
  - On The Beam..., 1965; Dodgers, Brooklyn Bum, 1965 World Series (Box 1)
  - Onward And Upward, 1965; Yankees, Angels, angel (Box 1)
  - [Orioles 4 ...], 1961-1966; Yankee players looking up at A.L. results on scoreboard (Box 1)
  - [Our Little Guy Must Be Growing Up...], 1961-1966; Mets, Mets kid, "Miss N.L. pennant" (Box 1)
  - The Pasty Eater, 1961-1966; Phillies, Colt .45s (Houston), Cubs, Mets, Giants, colt, bear cub (Box 1)
  - Play-Mates, 1961-1966; Mets, Astros, Mets kid, Colt .45s cowboy (Box 1)
  - Playmates, 1961-1966; Phillies, Giants, "Carpenter's kids" (Box 1)
  - Portrait Of A Self-Satisfied Gent, 1963; Mickey Mantle, Joe Pepitone, All-Star Game (Box 1)
  - Put Out More Flags, 1961-1966; Yankees, Mets, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Quiz Program, 1961-1966; Alfonso Ramon Lopez, White Sox, Indians, Yankees (Box 1)
  - Recording Secretary, 1964; Jim Bunning, Mets, Phillies, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - Reunion In Cooperstown, 1966; Casey Stengel, Baseball Hall of Fame, Babe Ruth, Ty Cobb, Lou Gehrig, Mel Ott, Walter Johnson (Box 1)
  - A Run On Sox, 1961-1966; Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - Show-Down, 1961-1966; Yankees, Orioles, White Sox (Box 1)
  - [Since The Yankee Season Started...], 1961-1966; Yankees, rain out (Box 1)
  - Stee-e-rike!, 1961-1966; National League umpires (Box 1)
  - Stormy Weather, 1966; Yankees, Tigers, Mets, Reds, Mets kid, Opening Day 1966 (Box 1)
  - [That The Yankees Win By Clobbering The Pretenders...], 1964; Yankees, Orioles, Yogi Berra, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - There Are Some He'd Like To Skip, 1961-1966; Mets, Mets kid (Box 1)
  - They Went That Way?, 1961-1966; Yankees, 6th place (Box 1)
  - Tim-b-e-r-r-r, 1961-1966; Harmon Killebrew, Twins, Yankees (Box 1)
  - To The Rescue!, 1964; Mets, Phillies, Mets kid, Phillies 1964 collapse (Box 1)
  - The Trophy, 1966; Yankees, Mets, Mets kid, Mayor's Trophy Game 1966, Mayor Robert F. Wagner, Jr. (Box 1)
  - [Two New Boys With Different Problems], 1964; Yogi Berra, Hank Bauer, Yankees, Orioles, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - Two-Week Vacation, 1961-1966; Yankees, travel agent (Box 1)
  - Up To His Old Tricks, 1961-1966; Mets, Cardinals, Mets kid, St. Louis Swifty (Box 1)
  - Watch The Birdie, 1961-1966; Yankees, Orioles, oriole (Box 1)
  - What Agenda?, 1961-1966; N.L. and A.L. presidents, Joint Major League Baseball Meetings (Box 1)
  - [When The Yankees Left Home Ten Days Ago...], 1964; Yankees, Yogi Berra, flying carpet, 1964 season (Box 1)
  - Wins Are Where You Find 'Em, 1961-1966; Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - [With The First All-Star Thing In The Books...], 1961-1966; Yankees, Angels, angel (Box 1)
  - [The Yankees And Dodgers Have Taken Off...], 1961-1966; Dodgers, Yankees, Brooklyn Bum (Box 1)
  - [The Yankees Were In First Place When...], 1961-1966; Yankees, White Sox (Box 1)
  - [Yankees, With a 4 Game Winning String...], 1961-1966; Yankees, Angels (Box 1)
  - You Can't Prove It In L.A., 1961-1966; Mets, Cubs, Leo Durocher, bear cub (Box 1)
  - Young Man's Burden, 1961-1966; Bobby Murcer, Yankees (Box 1)
- Basketball cartoons, 4
  - Dan Cupid In Spades, 1961-1966; Knicks, Celtics, Ned Irish (Box 2)
  - Metropolitan Standoff..., 1961-1966; NYU, Fordham, St. Francis, Manhattan, Pa Knickerbocker (Box 2)
  - Neighborhood Rumble, 1961-1966; NYU, Fordham, St. Francis, Manhattan, Pa Knickerbocker (Box 2)
  - Not Enough To Go 'Round, 1961-1966; NIT, NCAA Tournament (Box 2)
  - [Pre-Season Predictions...], 1961-1966; NYU, Syracuse, Lou Rossini, NIT (Box 2)
- Boxing cartoons, 20
  - As Maine Goes..., 1965; Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Lewiston (Maine) (Box 2)
  - Awsk 'Ennery, 1964; Henry Cooper, Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Miami (Box 2)
  - [Everyone Within 400 Miles...], 1965; Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Lewiston (Maine), Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - Feet Of Clay, 1961-1966; Cassius Clay (Muhammad Ali), crumbled statue (Box 2)
  - The Foundling, 1965; Lewiston (Maine), Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston (Box 2)
  - Hands Up!, 1966; Cassius Clay, Ernie Terrell, Houston (Texas) (Box 2)
  - The Hat Trick, 1966; Emile Griffith, Joey Archer, Dick Tiger (Box 2)
  - Hot Air, 1964; Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Miami (Box 2)
  - The Ice Box Kid, 1949; Joe Louis, Toots Shor (Box 2)
    acquired 1993, source unknown
  - The Kid Brother, 1961; Floyd Patterson, Ingemar Johansson, Raymond Patterson (Box 2)
  - [The Only Thing We Really Don't Know...], 1966; Cassius Clay, Cleveland Williams, Houston (Texas) (Box 2)
  - Q And A, 1965; Cassius Clay, Sonny Liston, Lewiston (Maine), Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - [Richard Ihetu Is A Personable Young Man...], 1963; Dick Tiger (Richard Ihetu), Joey Giardello, tiger (Box 2)
  - Shadow Boxers, 1965; Zora Folley, Oscar Bonavena (Box 2)
  - Situation Normal, 1963; Luis Rodriguez, Skeeter McClure, Knicks, Rangers, Madison Square Garden (Box 2)
  - Sonny Side Of The Street, 1963; Floyd Patterson, Sonny Liston, Cassius Clay, Henry Cooper, Billy Daniels, Doug Jones (Box 2)
  - Target For Tonight, 1966; Joey Archer, Emile Giffith (Box 2)
  - What'll Ya Bet?, 1963; Floyd Patterson, Sonny Liston (Box 2)
  - Who's Fighting Whom?, 1964; Cassius Clay (Box 2)
  - Who's Who, 1961-1966; Willie Pastrano, Joey Giradello, Emile Griffith, Carlos Ortiz, Ultimino Ramos, Eder Jofre, Pone Kingpetch, Willard Mullin (Box 2)
- Football (College) cartoons, 28
  - All For One, 1966; Notre Dame, Michigan State (Box 2)
  - Bad Day For Someone, 1947; Princeton, University of Pennsylvania (Box 2)
  - Book Learnin', 1964; Roger Staubach, Navy, Penn State (Box 2)
  - Bull In The China Shop, 1961-1966; College bowl schedule (Box 2)
  - Cat Expert, 1961-1966; Harvard, Yale, Ivy League (Box 2)
  - The Chosen Few, 1963; Roger Staubach, Dick Butkus, Bob Brown, Scott Appleton, All-America team selections (Box 2)
  - For The "Tie", 1964; Army, Navy, Roger Staubach, Wayne Hardin (Box 2)
  - Gotham Bowl, 1961; Ron Bull, Merlin Olsen, Utah State, Baylor, Gotham Bowl (Box 2)
  - Imagined...Or For Real?, 1963; Navy, Duke, Roger Staubach, devil, mid-shipmen (Box 2)
  - [The Ivy League This Year...], 1964; Princeton, Ivy League, tiger (Box 2)
  - The Jolly Roger, 1961-1966; Roger Staubach, Navy, Army (Box 2)
  - Kipling Was Right, 1966; UCLA, Penn State, Syracuse, Pittsburgh (Box 2)
  - Lucullan Fare, 1961-1966; Pro Football Draft (Box 2)
  - The Missing Pieces, 1964; Syracuse, Army, Yankee Stadium, Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - [Oh, Sure We Know...], 1963; West Virginia, Pittsburgh, mountaineer, panther (Box 2)
  - The Old Army Game, 1966; Army, Navy, Willard Mullin (Box 2)
  - [The Only Common Opponent...], 1963; Pittsburgh, Army, panther (Box 2)
  - Operation Fountain Pen, 1961-1966; College stars, NBC, CBS, Pro Football Draft (Box 2)
  - Pall Over Pasadena, 1966; Notre Dame, Purdue, USC, Rose Bowl (Box 2)
  - Peregrine V. Pedestrian, 1961-1966; Army, Air Force, falcon (Box 2)
  - Private Fight, 1963; Illinois, Big Ten (Box 2)
  - Re-Run, 1964; Roger Staubach, Carl Stichweh, North-South Game (Box 2)
  - R.I.P., 1965; Army, Paul Dietzel, free substitution rule (Box 2)
  - [Saturday You Can Tune In...], 1964; Utah, West Virginia, Liberty Bowl (Box 2)
  - Saturday's Orphans, 1947; Army, Notre Dame (Box 2)
  - Stone-Age Bunyan, 1965; WAC, two platoon football, free substitution (Box 2)
  - Swing It, 1963; Army, Navy, Cotton Bowl (Box 2)
  - The Vision Of Early Fall, 1963; College All-Star Game (Box 2)
- Football (Pro) cartoons, 36
  - Added Starters, 1966; Cardinals, Bears, Halloween (Box 2)
  - All Right! All Right!, 1961-1966; Giants, Cardinals, Jets (Box 2)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1963; Giants, Packers, Bears, Lions, Colts, bear, lion, colt (Box 2)
  - Ashes To Ashes..., 1964; Giants, Browns (Box 2)
  - Bone Of Contention, 1964; Giants, Steelers (Box 2)
  - A Day With The Patsies, 1966; Giants, Jets (Box 2)
  - Don't Ask, 1966; Giants, Cardinals (Box 2)
  - Double Feature, 1965; Giants, Jets, Cowboys, Bills, gun fighter, Buffalo Bill (Box 2)
  - Enter Pro-Football, 1964; Giants, Jets, Eagles, Mets kid (Box 2)
  - Fall Speed Ahead, 1961-1966; Giants, training camp (Box 2)
  - Final-Final, 1963; NFL/AFL All-Star games (Box 2)
  - Halp!, 1963; Giants, Eagles, Steelers (Box 2)
  - Heavy, Heay..., 1961-1966; Giants, Browns, Jim Brown (Box 2)
  - Home, Sweat Home, 1961-1966; Jets (Box 2)
  - Homecoming, 1964; Giants, Redskins, Sam Huff, Davis Cup, Dennis Ralston, Chuck McKinley, tennis (Box 2)
  - In His Hair, 1963; Giants, Jets, Packers, Allie Sherman, Weeb Ewbank (Box 2)
  - Just Can't Wait, 1966; Pro Football schedule (Box 2)
  - ...Meanwhile Back At The Wrench, 1965; Giants, Jets (Box 2)
  - Next!, 1966; Giants, Redskins, Native American (Box 2)
  - Not Much Of A Santa Claus, 1966; Giants, Cardinals, Santa Claus (Box 2)
  - O! What A Fall Was There..., 1966; Giants, Steelers (Box 2)
  - Pigskin Diet, 1961-1966; Jets, Bills, Joe Namath, buffalo (Box 2)
  - Poor Timing, 1961-1966; Bears, Packers, 49'ers (Box 2)
  - Pur-r-r-r-r-r-r, 1963; Giants, Eagles, Y.A. Tittle, Allie Sherman, eagle (Box 2)
  - The Raw Material, 1965; Giants, Jets, Allie Sherman, Weeb Ewbank (Box 2)
  - Reward In Miami, 1961-1966; Giants (Box 2)
  - Santa Claws!, 1963; Giants, Bears, Y.A. Tittle, bear, NFL Championship (Box 2)
  - Season's Greetings, 1961-1966; 4th Annual American Football Coaches All-American Game (Box 2)
  - Short Summer - Hot, But Short, 1961-1966; Giants, Jets, exhibition season opens (Giants/Bears in Ithaca) (Box 2)
  - Silver-Lining Department, 1961-1966; Giants, Jets (Box 2)
  - Super Bowl ($1,200,000.00 ), 1966; Packers, Chiefs, Native American, Super Bowl (Box 2)
  - [Tell Me Not In Mournful Numbers...], 1961-1966; Giants (Box 2)
  - Top Hand, 1961-1966; Jets, Chargers, horse (Box 2)
  - Wheeling and Dealing, 1964; Giants, Cardinals, St. Louis Swifty (Box 2)
  - The Wrecker, 1963; Steelers, Giants, Bears (Box 2)
  - You Explain It, 1964; Giants, Redskins, Cowboys, Cardinals, Jets (Box 2)
- Golf cartoons, 6
  - Bugged, 1963; Sam Snead (Box 3)
  - The Congressional, 1961-1966; The Congressional, tiger (Box 3)
  - Deep Drain The Cup, 1964; Tony Lema (Box 3)
  - Deep Fill The Cup..., 1965; Tony Lema, British Open (Box 3)
  - ...The Gang's All Here, 1961-1966; The Thunderbird, Pa Knickerbocker, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - I'm In The Rough, 1961-1966; U.S. Open (Box 3)
- Hockey cartoons, 6
  - The Art Critic, 1961-1966; Rangers, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Brothers Under The Skin, 1961-1966; Rangers, hockey fans, The New Breed (Mets fan) (Box 3)
  - A Good Round Figure, 1961-1966; Rangers (Box 3)
  - Hottest Thing On Ice, 1961-1966; Rangers (Box 3)
  - Our Heroes, 1961-1966; Rangers, sports writers (Box 3)
  - The Well Dressed Man, 1961-1966; Rangers, Maple Leafs (Box 3)
- Horse Racing cartoons, 38
  - Art Critics, 1961-1966; Speedy Scot, Realization Stakes, Frederick van Lennep, Ralph Baldwin, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - The Big Apple, 1961-1966; Aqueduct, last race of the season (Box 3)
  - The Bird Watchers, 1961-1966; Flamingo Stakes, Roman Brother, Northern Dancer, flamingo (Box 3)
  - Birds Of A Feather, 1961-1966; Flamingo Stakes, Hail to All, Native Charger, Johnny Sellers (Box 3)
  - Bon Voyage, 1961-1966; Kentucky Derby, No Robbery, John Graver (Box 3)
  - Cotton-Batting Candidates, 1961-1966; Sadair, Bold Lad, Bill Winfrey, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Don't Bet On It, 1961-1966; Kentucky Derby, Damascus, Willie Shoemaker, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Good Samaritan, 1961-1966; Aqueduct takes its annual break (Box 3)
  - The Horse's Mouth, 1961-1966; Bret Hanover, Richard Downing, Futurity Stakes, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - It Must Be Hay!, 1961-1966; Aqueduct, Nelson Rockefeller, Bob Wagner (Box 3)
  - A Little Piece Of Real Estate..., 1961-1966; Dapper Dan, Belmont Stakes (Box 3)
  - The Lock, 1961-1966; Bret Hanover, Adios, Commodore Stakes, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Meeting Themselves Coming Back, 1961-1966; Yonkers Raceway, harness racing (Box 3)
  - [Northern Dancer], 1961-1966; Northern Dancer, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - [The NYRA Hangs Up An Extra...], 1961-1966; Bob Ussery, Smart Deb, NYRA (Box 3)
  - ...Off Whose Noose?, 1961-1966; Cardigan Bay, International Stakes, Yonkers Raceway (Box 3)
  - [Old Timers Around Any Sports Beat...], 1961-1966; Overtrick, Realization Stakes (Box 3)
  - Only Money, 1961-1966; unclaimed winnings (Box 3)
  - Owner And Prop, 1961-1966; Jaipur, Manuel Ycaza, Donut King, Gotham Stakes (Box 3)
  - Pegged Out, 1961-1966; Manuel Ycaza, Iron Peg (Box 3)
  - Picture Horse, 1961-1966; Kelso, Suburban Stakes (Box 3)
  - Race Riot, 1947; Belmont (Box 3)
  - Right From The Horse's Mouth..., 1961-1966; Kentucky Derby prospects, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - Rolling Home..., 1961-1966; Kelso, Brooklyn Stakes (Box 3)
  - Roosevelt Raceway, 1961-1966; Roosevelt Raceway, Yonkers Raceway, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - The Runt, 1961-1966; Roman Brother (Box 3)
  - A Salute, 1961-1966; Flag Raiser, Bob Ussery, Preakness Stakes (Box 3)
  - Same Old Story, 1961-1966; Off Track Betting, New York State government (Box 3)
  - The Shoe Fits, 1961-1966; Willie Shoemaker, Bonjour, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - [Something Just Might Shake Out...], 1961-1966; Wood Memorial Stakes (Box 3)
  - Tempus Fugit, 1961-1966; Bowie Race Track (Maryland) season opens (Box 3)
  - [This Is The Day...], 1961-1966; Roosevelt Raceway season opens (Box 3)
  - [This Week N.Y. Thoroughbreds...], 1961-1966; Speedy Scot, Ralph Baldwin (Box 3)
  - Uniform Of The Day, 1961-1966; end of the racing season (Box 3)
  - Voodoo a-la-Louisville, 1961-1966; Damascus, Ruken, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - Who Ya Throwin' At?, 1961-1966; Candy Spots, No Robbery, Never Bend, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - The Will And The Way, 1961-1966; Bill Hartack, Bold Lad, Kentucky Derby (Box 3)
  - [The Winningest Horse Now Active...], 1961-1966; Theo Messidor, Willem Geersen, International Trot (Box 3)
- Track and Field cartoons, 9
  - The Badger Game, 1961-1966; Bob Hayes, Sam Perry, Fordham, NYAC Meet (Box 3)
  - The Cat And His Canary, 1961-1966; ICAAAA (IC4A) Indoor Meet, Harvard, Navy, Villanova, wildcat (Box 3)
  - [Despite The Royal Ukase...], 1961-1966; AAU Championships, NCAA, sanctioned competition (Box 3)
  - The Heavy Artillery, 1961-1966; Randy Matson, shot put, Texas A and M, Drake Relays (Box 3)
  - In The Clear, 1961-1966; Bob Seagren, pole vault, Millrose Games (Box 3)
  - The Natural, 1961-1966; Valery Brumel, high jump, NYAC Meet (Box 3)
  - On Your Mark..., 1961-1966; AAU, NCAA, sanctioning authority (Box 3)
  - One For The Money, 1964; long jump, AAU National Meet, 1964 Olympic team (Box 3)
  - [That Catapult They Use...], 1961-1966; John Pennel, pole vault (Box 3)
- Misc. Sports cartoons, 13
  - Agenda For 1964, artist as infant reading list (Box 3)
  - ...And, Among Other Things, 1964; 81st National Horse Show, LBJ, Goldwater (Box 3)
  - Drawing Board Re-Visited, 1961-1966; various New York sports figures, Willard Mullin returning from vacation (Box 3)
  - Go! I Said, 1961-1966; Mets, New York horse racing, the New Breed (Box 3)
  - The Groaning Board, 1961-1966; Yankees, Rangers, Jets, Giants, Knicks, Mets, Pa Knickerbocker (Box 3)
  - A Jolly Trio, 1961-1966; Rangers, Knicks, boxer, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - [Last Year Chuck McKinley...], 1964; Chuck McKinley, Wimbledon, Tennis (Box 3)
  - Objective Tokyo, 1963; 80th National Horse Show, Mary Mairs, Tokyo Olympics (Box 3)
  - Panning Out Pretty Good, 1964; Uncle Sam, Mt. Fujiyama, Tokyo Olympics (Box 3)
  - Pot-Pourri, 1964; Yankees, Mets, Giants, Jets, and misc. NY sports figures, Willard Mullin (Box 3)
  - That Commodity Called Youth, 1964; Scott Ethan Allen, Men's figure skating (Box 3)
  - To Each His Own..., 1961-1966; various sports, horses, camel racing, horseshoes, figure skating (Box 3)
  - Voice From Astern, 1961-1966; Constellation, yachting (Box 3)